<resources>
    <string-array name="club_name">
        <item>Barcelona FC</item>
        <item>Real Madrid FC</item>
        <item>Bayern Munchen FC</item>
        <item>Manchester City FC</item>
        <item>Manchester United FC</item>
        <item>Chelsea FC</item>
        <item>AC Milan FC</item>
        <item>Arsenal FC</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="club_description">
        <item>Futbol Club Barcelona, known simply as Barcelona and colloquially as Barça, is a professional football club based in Barcelona, Catalonia, Spain.<br />
            Founded in 1899 by a group of Swiss, English and Catalan footballers led by Joan Gamper, the club has become a symbol of Catalan culture and Catalanism, hence the motto "Més que un club" ("More than a club").
            Unlike many other football clubs, the supporters own and operate Barcelona. It is the third most valuable sports team in the world, worth $4.07 billion, and the world's third richest football club in terms of revenue, with an annual turnover of €648.3 million.<br></br>
            The official Barcelona anthem is the "Cant del Barça", written by Jaume Picas and Josep Maria Espinàs</item>
        <item>Founded on 6 March 1902 as the Madrid Football Club, the club has traditionally worn a white home kit since inception.<br />
            The word real is Spanish for "royal" and was bestowed to the club by King Alfonso XIII in 1920 together with the royal crown in the emblem.
            The team has played its home matches in the 81,044-capacity Santiago Bernabéu Stadium in downtown Madrid since 1947.
            Unlike most European sporting entities, Real Madrid's members (socios) have owned and operated the club throughout its history.</item>
        <item>FC Bayern was founded in 1900 by 11 football players, led by Franz John. Although Bayern won its first national championship in 1932, the club was not selected for the Bundesliga at its inception in 1963.<br></br>
            The club had its period of greatest success in the middle of the 1970s when, under the captaincy of Franz Beckenbauer, it won the European Cup three times in a row (1974–1976).
            Overall, Bayern has reached ten European Cup/UEFA Champions League finals, most recently winning their fifth title in 2013 as part of a continental treble. <br />
            Bayern has also won one UEFA Cup, one European Cup Winners' Cup, one UEFA Super Cup, one FIFA Club World Cup and two Intercontinental Cups, making it one of the most successful European clubs internationally and the only German club to have won both international titles.
            Since the formation of the Bundesliga, Bayern has been the dominant club in German football with 28 titles and has won 10 of the last 14 titles. They have traditional local rivalries with 1860 Munich and 1. FC Nürnberg, as well as with Borussia Dortmund since the mid-1990s.</item>
        <item>Manchester City Football Club is a football club in Manchester, England.
            Founded in 1880 as St. Mark's (West Gorton), it became Ardwick Association Football Club in 1887 and Manchester City in 1894.
            The club's home ground is the City of Manchester Stadium in east Manchester, to which it moved in 2003, having played at Maine Road since 1923.</item>
        <item>Manchester United Football Club, commonly known as Man United or simply United, is a professional football club based in Old Trafford, Greater Manchester, England,
            that competes in the Premier League, the top flight of English football. Nicknamed "the Red Devils",
            the club was founded as Newton Heath LYR Football Club in 1878, changed its name to Manchester United in 1902 and moved to its current stadium, Old Trafford, in 1910.</item>
        <item>Chelsea Football Club is a professional football club in London, England, that competes in the Premier League.
            Founded in 1905, the club's home ground since then has been Stamford Bridge.<br />
            Chelsea won the First Division title in 1955, followed by various cup competitions between 1965 and 1971.
            The past two decades have seen sustained success, with the club winning 23 trophies since 1997.
            In total, the club has won 28 major trophies; six titles, eight FA Cups, five League Cups and four FA Community Shields, one UEFA Champions League,
            two UEFA Cup Winners' Cups, one UEFA Europa League and one UEFA Super Cup.[6][7][8]</item>
        <item>Associazione Calcio Milan, commonly referred to as A.C. Milan or simply Milan, is a professional football club in Milan, Italy,
            founded in 1899.[5][6] The club has spent its entire history, with the exception of the 1980–81 and 1982–83 seasons,
            in the top flight of Italian football, known as Serie A since 1929–30.
        </item>
        <item>Arsenal Football Club is a professional football club based in Islington, London, England,
            that plays in the Premier League, the top flight of English football.
            The club has won 13 League titles, a record 13 FA Cups, two League Cups, the League Centenary Trophy,
            15 FA Community Shields, one UEFA Cup Winners' Cup and one Inter-Cities Fairs Cup.</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="club_image">
        <item>@drawable/img_barca</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_madrid</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_bayern</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_city</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_mu</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_chelsea</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_acm</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_arsenal</item>
    </array>

    <array name="league">
        <item>English Premier League</item>
        <item>English League Championship</item>
        <item>German Bundesliga</item>
        <item>Italian Serie A</item>
        <item>French Ligue 1</item>
        <item>Spanish La Liga</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="league_id">
        <item>4328</item>
        <item>4329</item>
        <item>4331</item>
        <item>4332</item>
        <item>4334</item>
        <item>4335</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="app_name">Football Club</string>
    <string name="vs">vs</string>
    <string name="lineups">Lineups</string>
    <string name="match_detail">Match Detail</string>
</resources>
